Chan Ka Long (陳家朗)

cklong0133@gmail.com | Github: https://github.com/KalongChan

Summary

An experienced Quality Assurance Engineer with 5 years experience in testing various native and web-based projects. Background in both Waterfall and Agile Scrum Methodologies for functional testing. Ability to learn quickly in high pressure situations in order to fully understand the requirement of a new project.

Education

Sep 2020 - July 2022 National Taipei University of Technology

Bachelor of Science in Information and Finance Management

Sep 2011 - July 2014 Hong Kong Institute of Vocational Education (IVE)

Higher Diploma in Customer Services for Aviation and Passenger Transport

Work Experience

May 2023 - Present Quality Assurance Engineer,

Cloras Technology Limited Taipei, Taiwan

- Perform tests on a web-based membership management system
- Establish testing standards and methods for the project
- Develop automation testing scripts with Playwright

Aug 2022 - May 2023 Quality Assurance Engineer,

Presslogic Taiwan Limited Taiwan Branch

Quality Assurance, Four Directions Limited

Taipei, Taiwan

- Create test cases and perform tests for digital media platforms
- Report and track bugs through Jira
- Perform various kinds of tests on iOS/Android devices and web platforms
- Work closely with developers and project managers to ensure quality of development

Apr 2018 - Jul 2020 Quality Assurance Engineer, Dreamshub Limited (formerly Lazybug Studio Limited)

Hong Kong

Hong Kong

- Plan & create test plan/test cases for various projects, mainly on online casino
- Prepare test data or fake data on staging environment
- Report, document and track software issues through bugzilla
- Develop and implement automation scripts to eliminate redundant manual tasks
- Ensure testing standards and procedures are followed on each project

- Create test plans/cases and perform tests for a mobile game app
- Prepare detailed test reports

Oct 2014 - Jul 2016

- Game level design and balancing
- Manage official social media network

SKILLS

Key Skills Jira, TestRail, Bugzilla, Postman, Selenium, Python, Java

Javascript, HTML, CSS, React.js, Next.js, MongoDB

Languages

Chinese(Cantonese) - Native
Chinese(Mandarin) - Proficient
English - Proficient
Japanese - JLPT N1